# YARDEN MATHIESON

FULL STACK DEVELOPER 

◆ TEL AVIV, ISRAEL 

◆ 0507749428

#### • DETAILS •

Tel Aviv Israel 0507749428 yardenm2710@gmail.com

Date of birth 27/10/1995

LINKS

My LinkedIn

My last project - Webit

My GitHub

My Portfolio

° SKILLS °

JavaScript

Vue.JS

React

Node.js

 ${\sf MongoDB}$ 

Git

SQL

SASS

jQuery

HTML & CSS

• LANGUAGES •

Hebrew

English

German

#### PROFILE

Full Stack Developer with knowledge and experience writing single-page applications using the latest WEB technologies such as React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, Redux, and VueX.

With a combination of strong visual design skills.

A team player, hard worker, focusing on problem-solving and detailed orientation, self-learner, responsible, and adapt quickly to a new environment.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Front End Developer at MISTERBIT Technological Solutions, Ramat Gan

July 2022 — Present

Developed and maintain high-scale SaaS applications for the company's clients using Vue.js, Vuex & SASS.

## Coding Course Instructor at MISTERBIT Technological Solutions, Ramat Gan

April 2022 — Present

Teach code from vanilla Js to advanced frameworks. Providing personal and group Code Reviews to students on the studied material. Developing and maintaining projects in MisterBit.

### Sales Manager at H.Z Corporation, Switzerland, Germany, Norway

December 2019 — January 2021

- Created the company's official website (Using WordPress)
- Trained and mentored new employees

#### EDUCATION

## Coding Academy, Ramat Gan

September 2021 — January 2022

- Three months of intensive learning including projects sprints web-based using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, MVC, Sass, Node.js, Rest API, MongoDB, Vue.js, Vuex, PWA, React, Angular, PHP and MariaDB / SQL

## Tzafit High School, Kefar Menachem, Israel

January 2008 — July 2014

• Full Matriculation

## ★ WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR IN MY NEXT CHALLENGE

- Solving complex technological tasks
- · Friendly work environment
- Interesting product I believe in
- · Growth opportunities
- Learning new technologies and programming concepts